Nyajoi Ramen Club Business Trip!
Let's have the best drink in our hometown Osaka!
Yes, that's right, this is the third activity of the Meow Joy Ramen Club!
Thank you for watching!
The person who will be eating ramen with us this time is
Alice!
My name is Alice Yamano! Please take care of her!
I'm very excited to be here because I didn't expect to be in Osaka for this shoot!
Why am I in Osaka today?
It's the day after the Miyagi Cold Tour Absolute Osaka!
Since Mr. Miyazu was able to come to Osaka
We are both from Osaka!
We are planning to eat delicious local ramen!
And what's more, today's restaurant is...
It's a popular restaurant that ramen lovers in Osaka will definitely know.
So please look forward to it!
Let's go there right away!
Since we're in Agis Osaka, please pretend to speak in Kansai dialect.
I'm going to eat ramen!
I'm looking forward to it!
I'm hungry.
There it is!
That's it!
Yes! So, today we have a new resident.
Mr. Menlouis, a new resident!
Thank you!
Your name sounds like Osaka, doesn't it?
Yes! This restaurant is called "Mentenai".
I heard that about 100 people stand in line for men-tenner.
I was allowed to stand in this popular restaurant today!
Thank you very much!
I looked at the tabelog.
I was surprised by the high rating!
I'm looking forward to it!
I heard that this restaurant is one of the top 100 restaurants in Japan.
I heard it's been on the list for 7 years in a row!
I didn't know that!
We were given a special seat today.
Let's go in right away!
Yes, sir! Well, I'd like to order right away, but...
We've already decided on the menu.
Oh, really?
Yes, this time we'll have the most recommended ramen.
The best way to eat ramen! That's why we've decided on the concept of "Let's eat the best ramen in the best way!
I've interviewed the restaurant staff and a famous Kansai ramen fanatic in advance.
I have prepared this tiger's roll for you.
I think I'll try it just like this!
So, we decided to eat the most recommended menu that the manager has researched!
There are three kinds of ramen in total
What did the two of us choose this time?
Well, there are macro, micro and origin.
Macro seems to be the most popular.
Oh, really! It says, "If you come here for the first time, you should try the macro dish.
As the name "macro" implies, it seems to be really popular.
I think we'll have the macro.
It seems that you can choose your favorite chashu pork!
There are thick slices, thin slices, and the thickest slices in the world!
What about you, Min-chan?
The best in the world?
Yes, I think I'll have the best in the world!
Let's line up with these!
You order Ramen Macro and World's Thickest Chashu.
Alice ordered the ramen with thick sliced pork!
Here we are!
I'm Ramen Macro, the world's thickest slice!
Wow!
Looks delicious!
Yes, yes, yes...
I'll have the original thick slice.
But it's big!
Thick slice is big.
The color of the soup is totally different.
It's the same soy sauce, but the color is different.
It's like it's lighter or darker.
Looks delicious!
Shall we start eating?
Ready?
Bon appétit!
I'll start with the soup!
Oh! Soup!
May I?
Looks delicious!
It's hot, but it's thick.
The taste of the shellfish?
Isn't it good? It's really good.
It's good.
I'm going to go ahead and try it, too.
Boo-hoo! I've never had soy sauce ramen like this before.
Boo-hoo! I'll eat it!
The texture is just right.
Yes, it's good!
Let's see that thick slice of char siu... Jersey, here you go.
I'm right there to eat it.
I've never seen it this size before.
I'll try it.
It's delicious.
This is a little too good.
Lately.
Yash Yakitori Pork?
Thick slices of roast pork soaked in a delicious ramen.
It's delicious.
I'm so happy.
It's ice cream in the ramen.
Yeah.
You probably don't know that.
That's for sure.
I'm so happy to be here for the third time.
I'm very happy.
I'm very happy too.
I've been watching you.
Really?
Twice?
Yes, I saw it.
Of course, I saw the episodes with Raina and Momoka.
For the audience.
Really?
Thank you.
No problem... a box of ramen noodles for Nuñez.
Yeah.
There aren't many girls who don't have an extra box of noodles.
That's right.
Ami Ozawa and Mizuageko.
These two are still in the ramen club.
that's right!
They belong to the second club.
You want them to join?
I'm in.
Okay.
Ramen Club
You're in!
I was wondering what you'd say.
I'll be happy if you say I'm awesome.
I'll be happy if you say it's awesome.
Let's eat ramen together.
Every restaurant we've filmed at...
I've had a lot of fans come to see me.
I'm sure you'll see a lot of fans there.
Please take a look at the human side
Please take a look.
Many of them are in Osaka.
It's delicious!
Amazing!
I'll make a comment here.
I'm actually
I don't like bamboo shoots.
What? Is that such a big deal?
I thought you liked pickled bamboo shoots.
You like bamboo shoots, right?
Like, "I'll eat it.
When we go out for ramen, he'll tell me.
I'm impressed when I eat menma every day, aren't I?
Even when I ate ramen every day, I tripled the amount of Noodles.
As expected, Noodles is 3 times more than noodles.
Like Menba-chan.
Why do you want to do this?
Number 2, well, that's the first reason, everyone says they want to go.
Really.
I don't know, but I like Pichon best among all the characters in the world.
I'm a Pichon fanatic and collect all his mugs and handkerchiefs.
I want to work with Pichon-kun.
It's no exaggeration to say that Pichon-kun is the symbol of Osaka.
I'd love to work with Mr. Pichon someday.
I'll be waiting for you.
I'm going to turn in alone tomorrow.
I'm going to eat now.
So, this Meow Joy Ramen club...
Every time we visit a café, we make a carta.
We make a carta.
Mm-hmm.
I'd like to read one this time, too.
Yes, sir.
I'll read it.
Here's a karuta from the Miyagi Ramen Club.
This is a karuta of the Miyagi Ramen Club.
It was really good! My eyes popped out!
If you live nearby or are in Osaka for work or pleasure, please stop by.
If you live nearby or are visiting Osaka for work or pleasure, please stop by!
Thank you for eating ramen with me.
So, if you eat ramen, too...
If you eat ramen, please post it in tomorrow's Miyagi Ramen Club!
If you like this video, please leave a comment, subscribe to our channel, or click the "Good" button.
I'm looking forward to seeing you all!
That's all for now, this is the Miyagi Ramen Club!
See you soon!